leaprate.com 2019-05-23

# Privacy Policy - LeapRate

LeapRate is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, store and use information on individuals that use this website. We strive to ensure that our personnel and those acting on our behalf obtain, use and disclose personal information lawfully and correctly.

Email Address

LeapRate provides the opportunity to its readers to sign up for our Forex Industry News email newsletter. The only information we ask for when you sign up to our newsletter is your email address, to which we will send the newsletter. LeapRate visitors can also opt in to receive periodic promotional emails. Subscribers to either the newsletter or the promotional emails can choose to unsubscribe at any time by clicking ‘unsubscribe’ at the bottom of any of the emails received, or by notifying us at info@leaprate.com.

Cookies

We may collect some information automatically from your computer, without notice such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, computer and connection information, browser type and version, operating system, Internet Service Provider (ISP), time stamps, banner ads you click, the URLs you come from and go to next, and a cookie number. The information is stored on Google’s servers.

LeapRate will sometimes place anonymous cookies or web beacons on your computer when you visit the site. We use these cookies and web beacons to recognize returning users, provide relevant content, measure traffic and activity on the site, monitor and improve our services and protect against fraud. You can block cookies by changing the settings on your browser (consult your browser help menu to find out how) but doing so may prevent us from delivering certain services to you. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site.

We also may allow advertisers to occasionally use our site and they may also use cookies on the site.  Advertisers’ use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, and we have no access to or control over these cookies.

Disclosure of Information

In certain cases, we may provide personal information to other third parties, such as advertisers, partners or for online advertising auctions. Where we provide personal information to third parties, other than for use on our behalf, it will be provided either in aggregated form that does not identify your identity, or in a form that does not link the information to you. In certain cases, such as information provided to our advertisers, we may provide non-personally identifiable identification (for example, gender) in connection with an IP address.

We will not sell, share, rent or trade your personal information with third parties other than as disclosed within this Privacy Policy unless we have your consent.

We may disclose your personal information to third-party vendors who provide services to us or facilitate or evaluate the sites or services, such as email service providers sending emails on our behalf.

We also may share your information as required by law in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process or in response to a law enforcement agency’s request; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as we reasonably believe appropriate to comply with applicable laws, regulations, orders, legal processes or government or regulatory requests, including tax authorities, as well as in order to comply with anti-money laundering laws and regulations. In such cases we reserve the exclusive right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.

We may transfer or assign your information, without any notice, and without a need to receive your consent, to any third party as a result of change of control, consolidation, merger, acquisition or reorganization of LeapRate.

Other than as set out above, you will be notified when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information.

Notification of Changes

This policy may change from time to time and we will post the amended terms on the LeapRate site. You should review our Privacy Policy periodically to remain informed of any changes. You agree to accept posting of a revised Privacy Policy as actual notice to you.

Your continued use of the site after any changes to this Policy have been posted (or, if applicable, notified) signifies your acceptance of those changes. If you do not agree to the revised Privacy Statement, please refrain from using our products or services and contact us by sending an email to info@leaprate.com.

You can also request that we no longer use your information by emailing us at info@leaprate.com. We may however retain some information if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud, assist with investigations, resolve disputes, analyze or troubleshoot programs, and take actions otherwise permitted by law.

Questions and Feedback

LeapRate is strongly committed to our relationship with you and want to be sure you understand the steps we have taken to protect your personal information. If you have questions or feedback regarding our privacy policy, you may direct them to info@leaprate.com and we will make every effort to answer your questions.

If you are not satisfied with our response, you have the right to make a formal complaint to the relevant data protection authority.

This Privacy Policy was updated in May 2018.
